{
	"name": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice",
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-1",
			"front": "Which of the following statements regarding fire ants is correct?\n\nA. Fire ant bites rarely cause anaphylaxis.\nB. Fire ants often bite a person repeatedly.\nC. Fire ant bites typically occur on the face.\nD. Most people are allergic to fire ant toxin.\nSee Common Allergens",
			"back": "Fire ants often bite a person repeatedly."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-2",
			"front": "Immediately after giving an epinephrine injection, you should:\n\nA. record the time and dose given.\nB. notify medical control of your action.\nC. reassess the patient’s vital signs.\nD. properly dispose of the syringe.\nSee Emergency Medical Care of Immunologic Emergencies",
			"back": "properly dispose of the syringe."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-3",
			"front": "Which of the following MOST accurately defines an allergic reaction?\n\nA. A direct negative effect on the body by an external substance\nB. An exaggerated immune system response to any substance\nC. Destruction of the immune system by an external substance\nD. A release of erythrocytes in response to a foreign substance\nSee Pathophysiology",
			"back": "An exaggerated immune system response to any substance"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-4",
			"front": "When administering epinephrine via auto-injector, you should hold the injector in place for:\n\nA. 3 seconds.\nB. 8 seconds.\nC. 15 seconds.\nD. 10 seconds.\nSee Emergency Medical Care of Immunologic Emergencies",
			"back": "3 seconds."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-5",
			"front": "A raised, swollen, well-defined area on the skin that is the result of an insect bite or sting is called:\n\nA. urticaria.\nB. a pustule.\nC. purpura.\nD. a wheal.\nSee Common Allergens",
			"back": "a wheal."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-6",
			"front": "The foreign substance responsible for causing an allergic reaction is called a(n):\n\nA. histamine.\nB. antibody.\nC. leukotriene.\nD. allergen.\nSee Pathophysiology",
			"back": "allergen."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-7",
			"front": "Urticaria is the medical term for:\n\nA. swelling.\nB. hives.\nC. burning.\nD. a wheal.\nSee Pathophysiology",
			"back": "hives."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-8",
			"front": "When an auto-injector is used to give epinephrine, the primary injection site is the:\n\nA. lateral portion of the thigh.\nB. medial portion of the thigh.\nC. lateral portion of the arm.\nD. medial part of the buttocks.\nSee Emergency Medical Care of Immunologic Emergencies",
			"back": "lateral portion of the thigh."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-9",
			"front": "A 38-year-old woman was bitten by fire ants while at the park. Your primary assessment reveals that she is semiconscious; has labored breathing; and has a rapid, thready pulse. She has a red rash on her entire body, and her face is swollen. You should:\n\nA. place her supine with her legs elevated.\nB. perform a rapid secondary assessment.\nC. assist her ventilations with 100% oxygen.\nD. locate the area where the fire ants bit her.\nSee Patient Assessment of an Immunologic Emergency",
			"back": "assist her ventilations with 100% oxygen."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-10",
			"front": "Which of the following sounds indicates swelling of the upper airway?\n\nA. Wheezing\nB. Stridor\nC. Rales\nD. Rhonchi\nSee Patient Assessment of an Immunologic Emergency",
			"back": "Stridor"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-11",
			"front": "While auscultating breath sounds of a patient who was stung multiple times by a yellow jacket, you hear bilateral wheezing over all lung fields. This indicates:\n\nA. enlargement of the bronchioles in the lungs.\nB. a significant amount of fluid in the alveoli.\nC. rapid swelling of the upper airway tissues.\nD. narrowing of the bronchioles in the lungs.\nSee Patient Assessment of an Immunologic Emergency",
			"back": "narrowing of the bronchioles in the lungs."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-12",
			"front": "The stinger from a honeybee should be:\n\nA. scraped away from the skin.\nB. squeezed with tweezers and removed.\nC. irrigated with copious amounts of water.\nD. left in place and covered.\nSee Common Allergens",
			"back": "scraped away from the skin."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-13",
			"front": "Two of the MOST common signs of anaphylaxis are:\n\nA. urticaria and angioedema.\nB. watery eyes and localized itching.\nC. hypertension and swollen hands.\nD. expiratory stridor and tachycardia.\nSee Pathophysiology",
			"back": "urticaria and angioedema."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-14",
			"front": "Epinephrine is indicated for patients with an allergic reaction when:\n\nA. the patient is anxious and tachycardic.\nB. wheezing and hypotension are present.\nC. the reaction produces severe urticaria.\nD. a paramedic is present at the scene.\nSee Emergency Medical Care of Immunologic Emergencies",
			"back": "wheezing and hypotension are present."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-15",
			"front": "Which of the following negative effects of anaphylaxis will be the MOST rapidly fatal if not treated immediately?\n\nA. Diffuse urticaria\nB. Upper airway swelling\nC. Systemic vasodilation\nD. Severe hypotension\nSee Patient Assessment of an Immunologic Emergency",
			"back": "Upper airway swelling"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-16",
			"front": "The effects of epinephrine are typically observed within _________ following administration.\n\nA. 1 hour\nB. 1 minute\nC. 30 seconds\nD. 30 minutes\nSee Emergency Medical Care of Immunologic Emergencies",
			"back": "1 minute"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-17",
			"front": "Common signs and symptoms of an allergic reaction include all of the following, EXCEPT:\n\nA. persistent dry cough.\nB. abdominal cramps.\nC. drying of the eyes.\nD. flushing of the skin.\nSee Patient Assessment of an Immunologic Emergency",
			"back": "drying of the eyes."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-18",
			"front": "Which of the following patients would MOST likely have a delayed onset of an allergic reaction?\n\nA. A 45-year-old male who ingested penicillin\nB. A 21-year-old female who inhaled pollen\nC. A 30-year-old male who was stung by a bee\nD. A 50-year-old male who was exposed to latex\nSee Common Allergens",
			"back": "A 45-year-old male who ingested penicillin"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-19",
			"front": "Which of the following would MOST likely provide clues regarding the source of a patient’s allergic reaction?\n\nA. The environment in which the patient is found\nB. The patient’s family history\nC. The patient’s general physical appearance\nD. The time of year in which the exposure occurred\nSee Patient Assessment of an Immunologic Emergency",
			"back": "The environment in which the patient is found"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-21-tag-multiple-choice-card-20",
			"front": "Chemicals that are responsible for the signs and symptoms of an allergic reaction to a bee sting include:\n\nA. leukocytes and epinephrine.\nB. the bee venom itself.\nC. adrenaline and histamines.\nD. histamines and leukotrienes.\nSee Pathophysiology",
			"back": "histamines and leukotrienes."
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-21",
		"label": "Chapter 21"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "multiple-choice",
			"label": "Multiple Choice"
		}
	]
}